<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Home on Santiago Moreno</title><link>https://santimj.com/</link><description>Recent content in Home on Santiago Moreno</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://santimj.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Complementary Skills &amp; Interests</title><link>https://santimj.com/other-interests/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://santimj.com/other-interests/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Languages, certifications, licenses, and hobbies that complement my professional work and enrich my perspective.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Engineering</title><link>https://santimj.com/engineering/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://santimj.com/engineering/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;This is an overview of my technical side. The starting point and where I always return to. A mix of working experience, hobbies, abilities and lots of dedication.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>My Sky</title><link>https://santimj.com/astrology/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://santimj.com/astrology/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;“It doesn’t matter whether you believe in these things or not. I share them here because I think they match me well so reading this page is a way to understand my own views on myself. It&amp;rsquo;s a different way to tell you about myself”.&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Personal Development</title><link>https://santimj.com/personal-development/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://santimj.com/personal-development/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;The practices and experiences that have shaped who I am. From formal trainings to years of living abroad, these are the tools and perspectives that help me understand myself, navigate relationships, and continue growing as a person.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>SMJ</title><link>https://santimj.com/smj/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://santimj.com/smj/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to my site!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Feel invited to explore it at your own rhythm. You&amp;rsquo;ll find different facets of my work and interests—each one something I can bring to various kinds of projects, depending on what you need.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m what you might call highly intellectually gifted, which in practice means I&amp;rsquo;ve always been deeply curious about how things work—systems, people, patterns. This has led me to explore many areas, as you&amp;rsquo;ll see in my professional and personal trajectory. It started in Lyon, France, where I studied bioinformatics and modelling at INSA, learned to live abroad, handle a new language, and navigate myself and my emotions in unfamiliar territory.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Teaching</title><link>https://santimj.com/teaching/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://santimj.com/teaching/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;I have a tendency to teach anything to anyone—music, dance, languages, mathematics, philosophy, enneagram—with a secret pleasure in finding the right metaphors and the proper terms to make complex ideas accessible. Teaching isn&amp;rsquo;t just about transferring knowledge; it&amp;rsquo;s about creating new worlds to expand someone&amp;rsquo;s mind, and therefore life.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>The Artist</title><link>https://santimj.com/the-artist/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://santimj.com/the-artist/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;A concise snapshot of my theatre, music, and dance projects, with media links collected alongside the main CV entries.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>